Long John Nebel Papers
Long John Nebel Papers
- Tapes
  - LJN All Night Show
    - "Kingdom Of The Cults" P. J. Sydney, Walter Martin, Rev. Robert Schrock, Stewart Robb, Will Ousler, Ernest Partridge, April 6, 1966; nebel_0405-0409; 5 reels (Oversize 21)
    - "Hamlet" (aired 1966 October 29) Rouben Mamoulian, Stewart Robb, Betty Wood, Miles Kreuger, April 10, 1966; nebel_0410-0411; 2 reels (Oversize 21)
    - "Sleep" Gay G. Luce, Julius Segal, Joseph Lampl, S. K. Fineberg, April 27, 1966; nebel_0412-0415; 4 reels (Oversize 21)
    - "The Martyrs" (aired 1966 July 13, repeated 1967 September 26) Jack Mendelsohn, Roy Schatt, Sanford Teller, April 28, 1966; nebel_0416-0417; 2 reels (Oversize 21)
    - "Youth And The Hazards Of Affluence" (aired 1967 March 9) Graham Blaine Jr., Lee Steiner, Candy Jones, May 13, 1966; nebel_0418-0419; 2 reels (Oversize 21)
    - "Valley Of The Dolls: A Second Look" Jacqueline Susann, Erika Freeman, Will Ousler, May 15, 1966; nebel_0420-0423; 4 reels (Oversize 22)
    - "Eichmann" G. Hausner, Kieran O'Doherty, May 15, 1966; nebel_0424-0426; 3 reels (Oversize 22)
    - "Power And Impotence" (aired 1966 August 20) Edmund Stillman, William Pfaff, Kieran O'Doherty, Robert Jorio, May 18, 1966; nebel_0427-0428; 2 reels (Oversize 22)
    - "Infidelity" Sam Blum, Jacqueline Susann, Lee Steiner, May 20, 1966; nebel_0429-0430; 2 reels, listed on box as reels 3 and 4 (Oversize 22)
    - "De-Romanization of Catholicism" (repeated 1967 April 8) Fr. James Scheuer, Msgr. Adamo, Edmund Wakin, Rev. Robert Schrock, May 21, 1966; nebel_0431-0433; 3 reels (Oversize 22)
    - (aired 1966 June 23, repeated 1967 October 12) Dr. Daniel Robinson, Dr. Howard Miller, Bernard Chorosch, May 29, 1966; nebel_0434-0435; 2 reels (Oversize 22)
    - "Behind Closed Doors" (aired 1966 November 26) Edward Costikyan, Lester Del Rey, Kenneth Knigin, June 1, 1966; nebel_0436-0437; 2 reels (Oversize 22)
    - (aired 1966 August 26) Dr. Thomas Matthew, Al Lottman, June 4, 1966; nebel_0438-0439; 2 reels (Oversize 22, 23)
    - "Showcase" (aired 1966 June 25) Roy Newquist, Jacqueline Susann, Candy Jones, June 9, 1966; nebel_0440-0441; 2 reels (Oversize 23)
    - "Lawyer's Ethics" (aired 1966 October 8) Jerome Carlin, Kenneth Knigin, Bernard Chorosch, June 16, 1966; nebel_0442-0443; 2 reels (Oversize 23)
    - "UFD" (aired 1966 July 1) Gray Barker, Frederik Pohl, James Moseley, Roy Schatt, June 17, 1966; nebel_0444-0445; 2 reels (Oversize 23)
    - "The Lolita Complex" Russell Trainer, Lee Steiner, Erica Freeman, Will Ousler, June 18, 1966; nebel_0446-0448; 3 reels (Oversize 23)
    - "Catholicism" Fr. Joseph Scheuer, Edward Wakin, June 24, 1966; nebel_0449-0452; 4 reels (Oversize 23)
    - (aired 1966 October 28) Richard Clarke, July 1, 1966; nebel_0453-0454; 2 reels (Oversize 23)
    - P. J. Sidney, July 21, 1966; nebel_0455-0458; 4 reels (Oversize 23)
    - George Ferber, Frederik Pohl, Lester Del Rey, July 28, 1966; nebel_0459-0462; 4 reels (Oversize 23, 24)
    - (aired 1966 September 9) Morton Gunty, Patrick Henry, Kay Stevens, August 4, 1966; nebel_0463-0464; 2 reels (Oversize 24)
    - "Justice Without Trial" (aired 1967 February 19, repeated 1967 November 26) Dr. Jerome Skolnick, Sanford Teller, Kieren O'Doherty, August 6, 1966; nebel_0465-0466; 2 reels (Oversize 24)
    - "The Save By Borrowing Technique," Carl Person, Al Lottman, Kenneth Knigin, August 10, 1966; nebel_0467-0470; 4 reels (Oversize 24)
    - P. J. Sidney, Sanford Teller, August 13, 1966; nebel_0471; 1 reel (Oversize 24)
    - "Rush To Judgment" (repeated 1967 March 21) Mark Lane, Roy Cohn, Kieran O'Doherty, August 17, 1966; nebel_0472-0475; 4 reels (Oversize 24)
    - "Humphrey Bogart" Joseph Hyams, Sanford Teller, Roy Schatt, August 18, 1966; nebel_0476-0479; 4 reels (Oversize 24, 25)
    - (aired 1966 November 6) Edward Risman, Morton Gunty, Pat Henry, Dee Anthony, August 24, 1966; nebel_0480; 1 reel (Oversize 25)
    - Rev. Robert Schrock, Seena Hamilton, August 26, 1966; nebel_0481-0484; 4 reels (Oversize 25)
    - (aired 1967 May 5) Jacqueline Susann, August 26, 1966; nebel_0485-0486; 2 reels (Oversize 25)
    - "The Smut Rakers" (repeated February 1967) Edwin Roberts Jr., Lyle Stuart, Martin Scheiman, August 27, 1966; nebel_0487-0489; 3 reels (Oversize 25)
    - (repeated 1967 July 30) Sterling Yates, Danny Crystal, August 31, 1966; nebel_0490-0492; 3 reels (Oversize 25)
    - Seena Hamilton, September 2, 1966; nebel_0493-0494; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 25)
    - "Public Relations And Psychology" Sidney Ascher, Sanford Teller, Dee Anthony, Jacqueline Susann, September 2, 1966; nebel_0495-0498; 4 reels (Oversize 25)
    - "Astrology" (aired 1966 October 16) Joseph Goodavage, Lester Del Rey, Stewart Robb, Will Ouster, September 7, 1966; nebel_0499-0500; 2 reels (Oversize 26)
    - "Opinion Of The Court" (aired 1967 June 18) William Woolfolk, Sanford Teller, Frederik Pohl, September 10, 1966; nebel_0501-0502; 2 reels (Oversize 26)
    - "Flying Saucers" (aired 1967 March 24, repeated 1967 December 14) Dominick Lucchesi, Jim Moseley, Sanford Teller, September 16, 1966; nebel_0503-0504; 2 reels (Oversize 26)
    - "Brass Rail" Pat Henry, September 17, 1966; nebel_0505-0508; 4 reels (Oversize 26)
    - "Brass Rail" Jacqueline Susann, Lee Steiner, Candy Jones, September 18, 1966; nebel_0509-0512; 4 reels (Oversize 26)
    - (aired 1966 October 26) Sanford Teller, Dr. Erica Freeman, September 22, 1966; nebel_0513-0514; 2 reels (Oversize 26)
    - (repeated 1967 February 8) Henry Morgan (comedian), September 23, 1966; nebel_0537-0540; 4 reels (Oversize 27, 28)
    - "Medicare" Alan Abel, Jeanne Abel, Sterling Yates, October 5, 1966; nebel_0515-0517; 3 reels (Oversize 26)
    - June Havoc, Murray Schwartzman, Dr. Howard Miller, October 6, 1966; nebel_0518-0520; 3 reels (Oversize 26, 27)
    - "Franchises" Sammy Kaye, Timothy Johnson, Sanford Teller, October 7, 1966; nebel_0521-0523; 3 reels (Oversize 27)
    - Dayton Allen, October 9, 1966; nebel_0524-0527; 4 reels (Oversize 27)
    - "Medicine vs. Religion" (repeated 1967 April 11) Dr. George Freidman, Rabbi David Hollander, Roy Schatt, October 12, 1966; nebel_0528-0530; 3 reels (Oversize 27)
    - "Spoiled Priest" Gabriel Longo, Sanford Teller, October 15, 1966; nebel_0531-0533; 3 reels (Oversize 27)
    - Bob Crosby, Sammy Kaye, George Frazier, Sterling Yates, Chris Crosby, October 21, 1966; nebel_0534-0536; 3 reels (Oversize 27)
    - "Civilian Review" (aired 1966 October 30) Norman Frank, Aryen Neier, October 27, 1966; nebel_0541-0542; 2 reels (Oversize 28)
    - "Spoiled Priest" Gabriel Longo, October 27, 1966; nebel_0543; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 28)
    - "Tower In Babel" Erich Barnauw, Gard Ray, Daniel Crystal, October 29, 1966; nebel_0544-0546; 3 reels (Oversize 28)
    - "The Boston Strangler" (repeated 1967 April 25) Gerold Frank, Frederik Pohl, Edward Spingarn, November 3, 1966; nebel_0547-0549; 3 reels (Oversize 28)
    - Daniel Fry, James Moseley, Lee Castle, Dayton Allen, November 5, 1966; nebel_0550-0552; 3 reels (Oversize 28)
    - "Election Night" Bud Lewis, Victor Lasky, Al Lottman, November 9, 1966; nebel_0553; 1 reel (Oversize 28)
    - "Phones" P.J. Sidney, November 11, 1966; nebel_0554-0557; 4 reels (Oversize 28)
    - "Euthanasia" Rev. Donald McKinney, Rev. Robert Schrock, Dr. Leslie Wenger, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, November 16, 1966; nebel_0558-0561; 4 reels (Oversize 28, 29)
    - "Our Hospital Crisis" (aired 1967 February 3, repeated 1967 October 19) Edwin Hoyt, Leon Goodman, S. K. Fineberg, November 18, 1966; nebel_0562-0563; 2 reels (Oversize 29)
    - "Off Madison Ave" (aired 1967 April 16, repeated 1967 October 31) David Lyon, Sanford Teller, Al Lottman, November 23, 1966; nebel_0564-0565; 2 reels (Oversize 29)
    - "Franchises" Tim Johnson, November 23, 1966; nebel_0566; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 29)
    - "Hypnotism" Joseph Lampl, Samuel Vandervirt, November 25, 1966; nebel_0567-0570; 4 reels (Oversize 29)
    - "Return Of Al Lottman" Al Lottman, December 1, 1966; nebel_0571-0572; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 29)
    - Rabbi Aaron Pearl, December 1, 1966; nebel_0573-0575; 3 reels (Oversize 29)
    - (aired 1967 May 5) Randi, Sanford Teller, December 2, 1966; nebel_0576-0577; 2 reels (Oversize 29)
    - "America's Political Dynasties" (aired 1967 January 20, repeated 1967 July 28, 1967 November 23) Stephen Hess, Victor Lasky, Al Lottman, December 3, 1966; nebel_0578-0579; 2 reels (Oversize 29, 30)
    - "Men's Fashions" Theodore Kaufman, Jack Shor, Bernard Toll, Sanford Teller, December 14, 1966; nebel_0582-0584; 3 reels (Oversize 30)
    - (aired 1967 August 11) Bill Mazer, Noel Behn, Edward Spingarn, December 16, 1966; nebel_0585-0586; 2 reels (Oversize 30)
    - "Computers" (aired 1967 January 19) Bud Lewis, Frederik Pohl, Arthur Elias, December 17, 1966; nebel_0587-0588; 2 reels (Oversize 30)
    - "Gems" Robert Crowningshield, Dr. Howard Miller, Candy Jones, December 22, 1966; nebel_0590-0592; 3 reels (Oversize 30)
    - Dr. Erica Freeman, Rev. Robert Schrock, December 23, 1966; nebel_0593-0595; 3 reels (Oversize 30)
    - (repeated 1967 July 29 and 1967 December 24) Dr. Joseph Consentino, Seena Hamilton, January 6, 1967; nebel_0599-0601; 3 reels (Oversize 31)
    - "The Passover Plot" (aired 1968 January 2) Hugh Schonfeld, Walter Martin, Will Ousler, January 12, 1967; nebel_0605-0607; 3 reels (Oversize 31)
    - "Voluntary Sterilization" (aired 1967 January 22, repeated 1967 July 29) Dr. H. Curtis Wood, Will Ousler, January 13, 1967; nebel_0608-0609; 2 reels (Oversize 31)
    - "Washington Expose" Jack Anderson, Sanford Teller, Noel Behn, January 15, 1967; nebel_0611-0612; 2 reels (Oversize 31)
    - Fr. Gommar De Paun, January 21, 1967; nebel_0614-0617; 4 reels (Oversize 31)
    - (aired 1967 April 14) Al Lottman, Seena Hamilton, Danny Crystal, January 26, 1967; nebel_0621-0622; 2 reels (Oversize 32)
    - George Frazier, Woody Allen (aired 1967 June 10), February 2, 1967; nebel_0393-0394; 2 reels (Oversize 20)
    - "Phones" P. J. Sidney, Alexander Exum, February 2, 1967; nebel_0627-0629; 3 reels (Oversize 32)
    - "A Sign For Cain" (Violence) Dr. Fred Wertheim, Dr. Howard Miller, Sanford Teller, February 3, 1967; nebel_0630-0632; 3 reels (Oversize 32)
    - "Hypnosis" Richard Kollmer, Joseph Lampl, James Donnelly, John Kolish, Joan Brandon, February 5, 1967; nebel_0635-0637; 3 reels (Oversize 32)
    - W. Semmelink, D. Nager, J. LeVitus, G. Bozonik, L. Finley, February 8, 1967; nebel_0638-0640; 3 reels (Oversize 32, 33)
    - "The Trial Of The Germans" Eugene Davidson, Bentley Kassal, Noel Behn, February 10, 1967; nebel_0641-0644; 4 reels (Oversize 33)
    - Anne Fogarty, Richard Kollmar, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, February 13, 1967; nebel_0624-0626; 3 reels (Oversize 32)
    - "Expo 67" (aired 1967 May 19) Michael Dibbins, Seena Hamilton, Dr. Howard Miller, February 15, 1967; nebel_0646-0647; 2 reels (Oversize 33)
    - "Hospitals" (aired 1967 November 15) Senator Seymour Thayler, Leon Goodman, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, February 16, 1967; nebel_0648-0649; 2 reels (Oversize 33)
    - "Wayne, N. J." Rabbi David Hollander, Rabbi Aaron Pearl, Joseph Kottler, Will Ousler, February 22, 1967; nebel_0652-0654; 3 reels (Oversize 33)
    - "Executive Breakthrough" Auren Uris, Dr. Hanna Kapit, February 24, 1967; nebel_0655-0657; 3 reels (Oversize 33)
    - Al Lottman, Richard Copland, March 1, 1967; nebel_0660-0661; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 34)
    - Dr. Theodore I. Rubin, March 1, 1967; nebel_0662-0665; 4 reels (Oversize 34)
    - (aired 1967 April 22) Gaston Cogdell, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Fr. James Scheuer, March 2, 1967; nebel_0667-0668; 2 reels (Oversize 34)
    - Rev. A. Reuben Gornitzka, Rev. Ernest Lilley, March 5, 1967; nebel_0670-0672; 3 reels (Oversize 34)
    - "UFO'S" (repeated 1967 June 11) John Keel, Noel Behn, Paris Flammonde, March 17, 1967; nebel_0681-0683; 3 reels (Oversize 34, 35)
    - (aired 1967 April 26) Otto Preminger, Roger Cares, Noel Behn, Seena Hamilton, March 19, 1967; nebel_0686-0687; 2 reels (Oversize 35)
    - Milton Levine, ? Hartman, ? Hilstead, March 25, 1967; nebel_0694; 1 reels (Oversize 35)
    - Austin Flett, April 14, 1967; nebel_0703-0704; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 36)
    - Fr. Gommar De Paun, April 15, 1967; nebel_0705-0707; 3 reels (Oversize 36)
    - (aired 1967 April 21) P. J. Sidney, Florence Kennedy, April 16, 1967; nebel_0708-0709; 2 reels (Oversize 36)
    - Sanford Teller, April 20, 1967; nebel_0710-0712; 3 reels (Oversize 36)
    - "The Healing Partnership" Dr. Bernard Steinzor, Dr. Howard Miller, Seena Hamilton, April 21, 1967; nebel_0713-0715; 3 reels (Oversize 36)
    - Max Lerner, Bentley Kassal, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, April 28, 1967; nebel_0718-0719; 2 reels (Oversize 36)
    - (aired 1967 June 27) Harvey Granat, Robert Metz, Sanford Teller, Al Lottman, May 5, 1967; nebel_0721-0722; 2 reels (Oversize 36)
    - "Advertising" Sean Fitzpatrick, Burt Waneteck, Sanford Teller, May 10, 1967; nebel_0724-0726; 3 reels (Oversize 37)
    - "Music" Robert Thiele, Danny Crystal, Dee Anthony, Sterling Yates, Sylvia Syms, May 11, 1967; nebel_0727-0730; 4 reels (Oversize 37)
    - "Fluoridation" (aired 1967 December 19) Dr. Albert Burgstahler, Dr. Sheldon Weiss, Samuel Vandervirt, May 14, 1967; nebel_0732-0734; 3 reels (Oversize 37)
    - Seymour Thaler, Joseph Kottler, Sy Fineberg, May 17, 1967; nebel_0735-0737; 3 reels (Oversize 37)
    - (aired 1967 August 18) Seymour Thaler, May 21, 1967; nebel_0739-0740; 2 reels (Oversize 37)
    - "Movies-Bolex" Ernest Wildi, Charles Reynolds, Sanford Teller, May 24, 1967; nebel_0742-0744; 3 reels (Oversize 37, 38)
    - "Obesity" Dr. Harvey Barnett, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Dr. Hyman Chartock, Betty Nation, May 26, 1967; nebel_0745-0747; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - "A Man In His Time" John L. Spivak, Rev. Richard Newhouse, Jay Wishner, Sanford Teller, May 27, 1967; nebel_0748-0750; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - "Middle Aged Crisis" Dr. Hanna Kapit, Seena Hamilton, Roy Schatt, May 28, 1967; nebel_0751-0753; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - "Crime In The Suburbs" David Loth, Rev. Robert Schrock, Burt Wanetik, Roy Schatt, June 3, 1967; nebel_0754-0756; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - "Triple Cross" (aired 1968 March 24) A. E. (Eddie) Chapman, Noel Behn, Sanford Teller, June 4, 1967; nebel_0757-0759; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - Henry Treflich, Arnold Treflich, Roy Schatt, Paris Flammonde, June 7, 1967; nebel_0760-0762; 3 reels (Oversize 38)
    - "Jackpot" Gary Stradline, Emerson Coyle, Jay Wishner, Roberta Kopper, June 9, 1967; nebel_0763-0765; 3 reels (Oversize 38, 39)
    - "The Life That Late He Led" (Cole Porter) George E. Ells, Miles Kreuger, June 15, 1967; nebel_0767-0769; 3 reels (Oversize 39)
    - "Jackpot" Celia Halk, Robert Bone, Edward Winter, Sanford Teller, June 16, 1967; nebel_0770-0772; 3 reels (Oversize 39)
    - "Flying Saucer Show" Art Ford, Mel Allen, Vivenus, John Wolfe, John Keel, Sanford Teller, Donald Singleton, June 25, 1967; nebel_0775-0777; 3 reels (Oversize 39)
    - "Motherhood" Seena Hamilton, June 27, 1967; nebel_0778; 2 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 39)
    - (aired 1967 October 28) Lynn Caine, Dr. Erica Freeman, Dr. Edward Spingarn, Paris Flammonde, July 2, 1967; nebel_0781; 1 reel (Oversize 39)
    - "Taxi Industry" (aired 1967 September 9) Egon Orbach, Edward Winter, Samuel Vandervirt, Roy Schatt, July 7, 1967; nebel_0782-0783; 2 reels (Oversize 39)
    - "Mammography" (aired 1968 February 4) Dr. Philip Strax, July 12, 1967; nebel_0784-0787; 4 reels (Oversize 40)
    - Joey Adams, July 12, 1967; nebel_0788; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 40)
    - "Advertising" (repeated 1967 August 22) Shirley Polykoff, Ruth Alampi, Sean Fitzpatrick, Sanford Teller, July 14, 1967; nebel_0789-0791; 3 reels (Oversize 40)
    - "Cancer Chemotherapy" (repeated 1967 September 19) Dr. Donald Cole, Samuel Vandervirt, July 21, 1967; nebel_0792-0794; 3 reels (Oversize 40)
    - "Our Crowd" (aired 1967 November 7) Stephen Birmingham, Leonard Sloane, Robert Frankel, Sanford Teller, July 27, 1967; nebel_0795-0797; 3 reels (Oversize 40)
    - "Astrology" Katherine De Jersey, Ruth Alampi, Edith Aynes, Ed Spingarn, August 2, 1967; nebel_0798-0801; 4 reels (Oversize 40)
    - "Men's Fashion" (aired 1967 October 24) Robert L. Green, Max Lefcourt, Bernard Toll, George Frazier, August 3, 1967; nebel_0802-0804; 3 reels (Oversize 40)
    - (aired 1967 November 1) Fr. James Kavanaugh, August 6, 1967; nebel_0805-0806; 2 reels (Oversize 41)
    - "Mensa" Dr. Edward Spingarn, Thomas W. Hamilton, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, August 9, 1967; nebel_0808-0810; 3 reels (Oversize 41)
    - "Tally's Corner" (repeated 1967 December 12) Dr. Eliot Liebow, Dr. Howard Miller, Alexander Exum, Bradford Crandall, August 12, 1967; nebel_0811-0813; 3 reels (Oversize 41)
    - "The Manchester Affair" (aired 1967 November 28) John Corry, Frederik Pohl, Al Lottman, August 16, 1967; nebel_0814-0816; 3 reels (Oversize 41)
    - "Famine 1975" William Paddock, Gary Stradling, Robert Cochnar, Samuel Vandervirt, Sanford Teller, August 18, 1967; nebel_0817-0819; 3 reels (Oversize 41)
    - Elaine Lorillard, Charles Hoefler, Seena Hamilton, Jay Wishner, August 19, 1967; nebel_0820-0822; 3 reels (Oversize 41)
    - "A Pictorial History Of The World's Greatest Trials" Edward Sagarin, Robert Cochner, Donald Singleton, Robert Frankel, August 23, 1967; nebel_0823-0825; 3 reels (Oversize 41, 42)
    - "Executive Search" Kurt Einstein, Emerson Coyle, Roland Finkleman, Arthur Witkin, August 24, 1967; nebel_0826-0828; 3 reels (Oversize 42)
    - Brad Crandall, August 25, 1967; nebel_0829-0831; 3 reels (Oversize 42)
    - "The Year Of The Quicksand" (Mercy Killing) Dr. Paul Mok, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Paris Flammonde, August 25, 1967; nebel_0832-0834; 3 reels (Oversize 42)
    - "Stock Market" J. M. Hartwell, Robert Metz, Al Lottman, Sanford Teller, August 26, 1967; nebel_0835-0837; 3 reels (Oversize 42)
    - "Sex Is Dead" Rev. Earl Brill, Rev. Richard Newhays, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Seena Hamilton, August 31, 1967; nebel_0838-0841; 4 reels (Oversize 42)
    - (aired 1967 September 2) Lester Del Rey, Frederik Pohl, Carol Pohl, Gary Stradling, Evelyn Del Rey, September 1, 1967; nebel_0842-0843; 2 reels (Oversize 42)
    - Maxine Fiel, Paris Flammonde, Jay Wishner, Sanford Teller, September 2, 1967; nebel_0844-0846; 3 reels (Oversize 42, 43)
    - "Long John Nebel's Stories" Sanford Teller, Robert Frankel, September 3, 1967; nebel_0847-0849; 3 reels (Oversize 43)
    - "Catholic Traditionalist Movement" (aired 1967 October 31) Fr. Gommar De Paun, September 6, 1967; nebel_0850-0852; 3 reels (Oversize 43)
    - George Frazier, Melanie Toyofuku, September 14, 1967; nebel_0856-0859; 4 reels (1 reel 1/4"x1200') (Oversize 43)
    - Hinton Sisters, September 15, 1967; nebel_0860; 1 reel (1/4"x600') (Oversize 43)
    - Jane Morgan, September 15, 1967; nebel_0861; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 43)
    - (aired 1967 October 14) Al Kasha, Edward Spingarn, September 22, 1967; nebel_0864-0866; 3 reels (Oversize 43, 44)
    - "The Beautiful People" (aired 1967 October 17) Marilyn Bender, Seena Hamilton, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, September 24, 1967; nebel_0867-0869; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - "The Unexplained" (repeated 1967 November 23) Allen Spraggett, James Randi, Stewart Robb, Sanford Teller, September 27, 1967; nebel_0870-0872; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - "Murder One" (aired 1967 November 21) Richard Kollmar, Paris Flammonde, Rev. Robert Schrock, September 29, 1967; nebel_0873-0875; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - "Riots USA." "Study Of Ellis Island" (aired 1968 January 21) Dr. Willard Heaps, Al Lottman, Roy Schatt, Samuel Vandervirt, September 30, 1967; nebel_0876-0878; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - "Myths Of The Space Age" (aired 1968 May 26) Daniel Cohen, Frederik Pohl, Sanford Teller, October 4, 1967; nebel_0879-0881; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - "Bashful Billionaire" (aired 1967 November 24) Albert Gerber, Al Lottman, Robert Cochnar, October 8, 1967; nebel_0884-0886; 3 reels (Oversize 44)
    - Saul Kent, October 15, 1967; nebel_0888; 1 reel (Oversize 45)
    - "Photography" John Durniak, Karl Breford, Sanford Teller, Samuel Vandervirt, October 18, 1967; nebel_0889-0891; 3 reels (Oversize 45)
    - "Black Power Establishment" William Worthy, George Frazier, Donald MacLean, Robert Cochnar, October 20, 1967; nebel_0892-0894; 3 reels (Oversize 45)
    - Jacqueline Susann, Marilyn Bender, Ann Fogarty, Seena Hamilton, October 29, 1967; nebel_0895-0897; 3 reels (Oversize 45)
    - "Jungle For Sale" (aired 1968 January 23) Henry Trefflich, Dr. Howard Miller, Robert Frankel, November 2, 1967; nebel_0899-0901; 3 reels (Oversize 45)
    - "Phones" (aired 1968 May 5) Dr. S. D. Klotz, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, November 3, 1967; nebel_0902-0904; 3 reels (Oversize 45)
    - "The Farther Shores Of Politics" (aired 1968 April 3) George Thayer, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Stephen Elias, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, November 4, 1967; nebel_0905-0907; 3 reels (Oversize 45, 46)
    - "The Political Principles Of Robert A. Taft" Russell Kirk, Al Lottman, Bentley Kassal, November 9, 1967; nebel_0908-0910; 3 reels (Oversize 46)
    - "Forensic Pathology" Dr. Cyril Wecht, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Rev. Robert Schrock, Bob Frankel, November 11, 1967; nebel_0911-0913; 3 reels (Oversize 46)
    - "Young Divorcees" Lissa Charell, Ruth Dickson, Joan Crosby, Seena Hamilton, Al Lottman, Robert Frankel, November 17, 1967; nebel_0915-0921; 7 reels (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 46)
    - "The Ageless Woman" (repeated 1968 June 2) Dr. Sherwin Kaufman, Terry Garrity, November 25, 1967; nebel_0922-0924; 3 reels (Oversize 46)
    - "Money" Dayton Allen, November 28, 1967; nebel_0925; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 46)
    - "The Great Radio Heroes" James Harmon, Leonard Sloane, Sanford Teller, Judith Teller, November 29, 1967; nebel_0927-0929; 3 reels (Oversize 46, 47)
    - "The Code Breakers" (aired 1968 April 7) David Kahn, Noel Behn, Bentley Kassal, November 30, 1967; nebel_0930-0932; 3 reels (Oversize 47)
    - Dr. Harold Greenwald, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Seena Hamilton, Will Ousler, December 2, 1967; nebel_0934-0936; 3 reels (Oversize 47)
    - "Judaism: Orthodox vs. Reconstructionist" Rabbi Ira Eisenstein, Rabbi David Hollander, Sanford Teller, December 3, 1967; nebel_0937-0939; 3 reels (Oversize 47)
    - "The Politics Of Honor: Adlai Stevenson" Kenneth Davis, Al Lottman, Don MacLean, December 7, 1967; nebel_0940-0942; 3 reels (Oversize 47)
    - "Private Screenings" John Simon, Seena Hamilton, Robert Cochnar, Paris Flammonde, December 9, 1967; nebel_0943-0945; 3 reels (Oversize 47)
    - Phil Foster, Sanford Teller, December 10, 1967; nebel_0946-0948; 3 reels (Oversize 47, 48)
    - "Music Show" Miles Kreuger, Sanford Teller, Alexander Exum, December 13, 1967; nebel_0949-0951; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - "A Girl's Guide To Men On The Make", December 14, 1967; nebel_0953-0955; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - "Advertising" Judy Wald, Roger Levinson, Sandy Teller, December 15, 1967; nebel_0957-0959; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - "Psychology Of Poverty" Dr. Herbert Greenberg, Dr. Emerson Coyle, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Donald Singleton, December 16, 1967; nebel_0960-0962; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - Dr. Carlton Fredericks, Samuel Vandervirt, December 20, 1967; nebel_0963-0965; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - "Transplants" Dr. George A. Friedman, Will Ousler, Paris Flammonde, December 21, 1967; nebel_0967-0969; 3 reels (Oversize 48)
    - "Fads, Follies And Delusions" Paul Sann, Sanford Teller, December 22, 1967; nebel_0970-0972; 3 reels (Oversize 49)
    - Jean Shepherd, December 23, 1967; nebel_0974-0975; 2 reels (Oversize 49)
    - "Psychiatry" Dr. Harvey R. Greenberg, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Paris Flammonde, December 28, 1967; nebel_0976-0978; 3 reels (Oversize 49)